{
    "code_debugging_basic": [
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(2 + '3');` print?",
            "options": [
                "5",
                "23",
                "NaN",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "23"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(3 == '3');` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "Syntax Error",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(3 === '3');` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "Syntax Error",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is `typeof NaN`?",
            "options": [
                "'number'",
                "'NaN'",
                "'undefined'",
                "'object'"
            ],
            "answer": "'number'"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(null == undefined);` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "Syntax Error",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(typeof []);` print?",
            "options": [
                "'object'",
                "'array'",
                "'undefined'",
                "'string'"
            ],
            "answer": "'object'"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does `console.log(Boolean(0));` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "0",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does `console.log([] == 0);` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "NaN",
                "undefined"
            ],
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log(5 < 6 < 7);` print?",
            "options": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "NaN",
                "Syntax Error"
            ],
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will `console.log('5' - 3);` print?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "8",
                "'53'",
                "NaN"
            ],
            "answer": "2"
        }
    ]
}